<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LUSW</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="palette">color palette</string>
    <string name="legend">Legend</string>
    <string name="settings">settings</string>
    <string name="permission_statement">We did not find available application usage information, it may be because you did not grant us the permission to obtain it. We hereby promise that the software does not have any networking function, and will not upload or collect any of your application usage information. The information granted by the permission is only used for wallpaper generation and local display of application usage.</string>
    <string name="authorization">go to authorization</string>
    <string name="default_group_name">other</string>

    <string name="unit_hour">%1$d time</string>
    <string name="unit_minute">%1$d points</string>
    <string name="unit_second">%1$d second</string>
    <string name="unit_millisecond">%1$d milliseconds</string>
    <string name="group_name">group name</string>
    <string name="confirm">OK</string>
    <string name="blank_content">Please enter valid content</string>
    <string name="content_consistent">please change a name</string>
    <string name="add">add</string>
    <string name="guide_main_title">Welcome to LUSW \n (Lollipop usage stats wallpaper) \n Here is a brief introduction to how the application is used:</string>
    <string name="guide_legend">Here you can set the corresponding color for each application separately</string>
    <string name="guide_palette">Here, you can configure the colors you like, and you can also set up a nice name for them</string>
    <string name="guide_settings">Here you can adjust some additional preferences, and you can also learn about the author’s information</string>
    <string name="guide_help">When you don’t know what to do, you can click this button, it will give you some tips</string>
    <string name="guide_palette_title">Here, you can adjust the color you like. \nThe following is a brief introduction to how to use it:</string>
    <string name="guide_add">You can add colors by clicking on it</string>
    <string name="click">click</string>
    <string name="guide_click_palette_card">You can click on the color card to adjust the color or its name</string>
    <string name="drag">drag and drop</string>
    <string name="guide_drag_palette_card">You can also press and hold the color card to trigger the drag sort, and rearrange the number for the color you like</string>
    <string name="swipe">sliding</string>
    <string name="guide_swipe_palette_card">You can also slide the color card to the screen or outside of the card to remove a color card.</string>
    <string name="guide_legend_title">Here, you can associate a color you like for each application. \nThe following is a brief introduction to how to use it:</string>
    <string name="copyright">from Lollipop\n(https://github.com/Mr-XiaoLiang/)</string>
    <string name="wallpaper_update_delay">wallpaper refresh time</string>
    <string name="swap">exchange mode</string>
    <string name="build">build mode</string>
    <string name="guide_legend_swap">It can help you switch the exchange mode, in the exchange mode, you can easily switch colors for each application</string>
    <string name="guide_legend_build">It can help you switch the build mode, in the build mode, you can quickly specify the color for the application</string>
    <string name="apply">Apply</string>
    <string name="generate">Generate</string>

    <string name="apply_wallpaper_success">Wallpaper is set successfully</string>
    <string name="apply_wallpaper_error">Wallpaper setting failed</string>
    <string name="guide_apply">You can quickly set LUSW as your wallpaper through it. If you can’t find LSUW on the wallpaper setting page of the system, then it may help you</string>
    <string name="wallpaper_animation">Enable animation</string>
    <string name="wallpaper_animation_summary">After closing, the wallpaper will not show transition effects when it appears. But this will not save you power.</string>
    <string name="menu">Options</string>
</resources>